我只是越来越焦躁不安了，Dyson
I'm just...I'm getting restless,Dyson.
我记得的最后一件事，是从木豆酒吧被劫走
The last thing I remember is being taken from the Dal
然后就是在树林里狂奔
then waking up in the woods.
我不能一直逃避，等着答案自己出现
I can't keep hiding,waiting for answers.
我们得等Una Mens那帮人安顿下来
Gotta lay low until the Una Mens settle down.
他们不就是想杀我嘛，排个队！取个号！
So they want me dead. Line up! Take a number!
欢迎加入捕杀淫妖俱乐部！我还需要继续吗？
Welcome to the club! Should I keep going?
这事比你想象的严重多了，Bo
This is bigger than you think,Bo.
咱古老的Una Mens法力无边
The Una Mens power is ancient.
噔噔噔
Dun dun dun.
我是认真的
I'm serious.
对不起嘛
I'm sorry.
但是华丽的委员会？老掉牙的法律？
But fancy councils? Ye old rules?
我现在真的不想去想这些了
It's just, it's the last thing on my mind.
那你想要聊聊你正在想的事么？
You want to talk about that first thing on your mind?
有消息吗？
...any word?
最近没有
Not lately.
但远离这些未知的东西对她来说更好
But it's better that she stays away safe with all of these unknowns.
Lauren很聪明，她会照顾好自己的
Lauren's smart, she can handle herself.
好吧，既然我要自己保护自己
Well, since I have to protect myself
不被那些未知的事情伤害
from all these unknowns...
那我应该要先来一发
I should get a hit. Below the belt.
你有点不一样了啊
Something is different about you.
嗯...看来你很喜欢嘛，非常喜欢
Well... you seem to like it. In a huge way.
那是甚？
What was that?
不知道，水管老化？
I don't know.Old pipes?
本作品片源来自互联网，仅供个人影视制作学习交流之用
任何组织和个人不得公开传播或用于任何商业盈利用途
挪威金毛的胡须最有爱了字幕组  r(st)q
英文字幕：来自互联网    翻译：Neffititi，BenedettaL，李夹碎，Momou
校对：Momo酱，李夹碎，潜行的五    特效、精校：潜行的五    压制：Joy
发布：百度贴吧Tamsin后援群
资源下载请关注瓦尔基里字幕组官方微博
4x04 - Turn to Stone
好了，别激动忍忍！
All right,less hooch,more tooch!
嗷，嗷，嗷！
Owww-owww...
好了,好了，快弄完了，深呼吸，深呼吸
Okay,okay,one more knot.Just breathe,just breathe.
梳好了，梳好了
There you go.There you go.
搞定
Done.
额滴神，一根头发都没掉耶
God,not a single strand.
我不想跳电臀了
I'm done twerking out.
我可以吃芝士条吗
Can I have Cheezies?
*加拿大售卖的一种芝士味膨化食品*
哎当然可以啦
Yes,you can have Cheezies.
谢啦
Thank you.
我去
Ugh!
Kenz,Trick的火圈又抽风了
Kenz,Trick's Ignis Rim is acting up again.
啊，来了！不好意思，我可能设置错了
Ugh, coming! Sorry,I probably just set it up wrong.
它应该只阻挡邪恶的Fae才对
It's only supposed to block out malicious Fae.
噢，我太高兴你终于回家了
Oh,I'm so glad you're home.
来抱抱
Come here.
即使你浑身都是健身汉子般的臭汗，我也不介意
You smell like sweaty gym-dude and I don't even care.
呃，Kenz，我只离开了一个小时啊
Uh, Kenz, I've been gone an hour.
不是我不喜欢啊
And not that I mind
但是这缠绵无止的抱抱是要抱到哪个世纪？
but how long is this incessant hugging gonna last?
要抱到我忘记你曾经离开过为止
As long as it takes to forget you were ever gone.
芝士条？
Cheezie?
不了，我刚吃完，饱着呢
No.I'm good,I already ate.
Dyson和我刚刚才...
Dyson and I just...
噢！在那个那个幼齿的谁前面不能说
Oh! Not in front of the B-A-B-Y  V-A-L-K... E?
还是，怎么拼来着？
Or is it,Y?
我才不是幼齿！
I'm not a baby!
我都快两周大了~谢谢
I'm almost two weeks old.Thank you.
好了，小萝莉 你还记不记得你老大是谁
All right, tweener 'tude. You remember who you work for yet?
我都说过了, 不记得, 那叫前世的记忆好伐
I already told you,I don't remember.It's called a previous life,okay?
目前我只记得我是黑暗系
So far,all I know is that I'm Dark.
那就是说，你知道的比你告诉我的要多咯
Which makes me think you know more than you're telling me...
噢, 你懂的, 这个年纪的娃儿嘛, 你拿她有什么办法呢?
Oh, you know, kids this age. Whaddya gonna do?
你知道吗，别管家里的破事了
You know what? Screw club house arrest.
嗯！咱们出去玩儿吧
Mm! Let's go out.
那这个芝士味小萝莉怎么办?
What about Cheezie breath over here?
嘿, 小塔
Hey, Lil' T.
你是想跟着姐姐们 超级无聊 一点都不好玩
Do you wanna come out with us? Totally boring,not fun.
还是想留在这个安全的小窝儿
Or do you want to stay in safety rim zone
继续看X档案
and watch the X-Files again?
X档案~棒！
X-Files. Yes!
搞定嗯嗯
Done.Mm!
酒！太棒了！
... drinks! Yeah!
为我们干杯
Drink to us.
嗯, 这儿像被占领的法国一样
Mmm.It is like occupied France in here.
这要哭的调调是怎么回事
What's with the cry tunes?
Una Mens来了 所有的娱乐活动都没了
Una Mens come to town, errrrything shut down.
哎 我还想着出来疯一把呢
Yeah well, I was hoping for a real night out.
那个，抱歉咯春假小妞
Well, sorry Miss Spring Breaker.
我答应过狼叔带你去些安全的地方的
I promised Dyson I'd take you somewhere safe.
噢！那你还记得一股黑烟从把我从这儿劫走了吧
Oh! You remember a cloud of black smoke kidnapped me here, right?
记得
Right.
我们对这个Wanderer有任何了解吗
Do we know anything about this Wander...
啊 我不想说这个
... Ahhh. I don't feel like talking about it.
老娘要跳舞
I wanna dance.
你认真的？在这？悲伤小镇？
Are you for real? Right here? In Sadville?
酱才对嘛
Now that is more like it.
淫妖回来啦
Bobo returns.
还带了个新属性？
With bonus features...?
嘿
Hey!
你带来了吗
Did you bring it?
我赶时间
I'm in a rush.
喂，又是廉价样品？
What? Flip flop sample sale?
我受够了骗小孩的把戏 我要来真的
I'm done with the kiddy toys. It's Tonka Truck time.
*Tonka Trucks 著名玩具公司Tonka的标志产品*
你做梦都付不起永久性技能的
You can't even dream to afford for permanent powers.
你连我给你的都买不起
You can't even pay me for what I supply.
听着 我会付你的
Look, you will get paid...
只要我的技能不会再消失，Massimo
as soon as my powers stop fading. Massimo.
Kenzi? Bo?
穆德？斯卡丽？
...Mulder? Scully?
*Mulder and Scully x档案的主角*
哦买高的， 你们在这作甚？
Oh my god, what are you doing here?
*辣妹组合的著名歌曲*
恋爱守则一二三
So here's a story from A-to-Z
要和姐厮守哦你要听清楚哦
you wanna get with me you gotta listen carefully
梅兰妮大姐大狂放又不羁
We got Em in the place who likes it in your face.
高高在上G 随和小V 高贵典雅
We got G like MC who likes it on an.Easy V doesn't
她是个淑女哦 至于我 你会明了
come for free. She's a real lady, as for me, ah you'll see.
把你推倒 任姐调教
Slam your body down and wind it all around.
Slam your body down and wind it all around!
你要和姐长相厮守啊
If you wanna be my lover.
就要搞定我闺蜜
You gotta get with my friends. You gotta get with my friends.
相亲相爱啊 闺蜜永不分离
Make it last forever friendships never end...
惊喜！你生气了吗？
Surprise! Are you so mad?
事实上 我觉得那酷呆了
Actually, that was freakin' incredible!
邪恶一回真是爽爆了
It feels so good to be bad.
Kenzi 我们被打劫了
Kenzi. We've been robbed.
Tamsin
Tamsin.
我想我又长大了
I think I grew again.
有人闯进我家里 陌生人
People were in our home.Strangers!
对二手破家具有特殊癖好的陌生人
Strangers with great taste in thrift shop furniture.
你要我给你拿点什么吗？咖啡或者坐一下？
Would you like me to get you something?A coffee or chair to break?
不管谁干的 姐要灭了他
I'm gonna break whoever did this.
我们家还有个小孩呢
We had a child in the home!
...之类的 呃 会是Una Mens干的吗
Sort of. Ugh, could this be Una Mens?
不会 他们不是贼
No,they're not thieves.
物质上的东西他们没兴趣
Material possessions don't interest them.
或者这可能不关异种的事
But maybe this isn't Fae-related at all.
可能只是普通小毛贼
Maybe it's just a good old break and enter.
即使放了火圈人类也还是可以进去
If that rim was up,humans could still enter.
不管他是不是异种，没有人能到我家拿我的东西
Fae or not, no one comes into my house and takes what's mine.
你知道 要是你想放松一下 我们可以 嗯
You know, if you need to unwind later, we could, uh...
去购物
Go shopping.
是啊，去购物
Go shopping,yeah.
那么要是你表现好的话，你可以进所有的商店
Well, if you're good, you can go in all the stores.
嗯 要是你表现好的话 我会刷爆你的信用卡
Well if you're good, I'll max out your credit cards.
两次
Twice.
我能一起么？
Can I come?
我要去查一个重要的线索了
I've got a suspicious lead to track.
让我帮你
Let me help.
你已经在帮我了
Oh,you already are.
等我去个洗手间，回来再跟你说是怎么回事
I'll explain when I get back from the facilities!
BO！厕所在...另一头...
Bo! The bathroom is...the other way.
哎，我成保姆了
And... I'm babysitting.
介妹纸是谁？
Who's that girl?
这个人失踪了，你和我要去找她
Someone who's lost. And you and I need to find her.
这全都是我的错，我竟然相信他们了
This is all my fault.I believed them...
他们告诉过我不会伤害你的
They told me they wouldn't hurt you.
他们是谁？
Who are "they"?
你好，好久不见Lauren
Hello. Long time no see, Lauren.
还是说我应该叫你...Karen
Or should I call you…Karen.
快回复啊，Massimo
Come on, Massimo.
我有钱包还有鞋子都可以给你...
I've got wallets to lift; shoes to covet...
卧槽！神马情况？！
Ow! What the hell?!
喂！！
Hey!!
好吧，我的御用香车和大杯摩卡冰拿铁呢？
Okay, where's my usual SUV and Venti-Mocha-Iced-latte?
*Venti(字面意思20) 指20盎司一杯的咖啡，即星巴克里的大杯*
不给钱的顾客没有贵宾级的服务
No VIP treatment for customers that don't pay.
他这是在给信息呢
He's sending a message.
那你...你给他发个信息
Well you...you give a message that
他可以解开我的塑料手铐拿去铐他的小德炉伊
he can take this zip tie and put it around his tiny druid...
*意指Massimo的男性器官*
喂？！花生神马鸟？
Hello?! What's happening?
三比零，是我bo
Three-nothing, Bo.
拿走我们的东西可以，但你绝对拿不走我家KENZI
Take our things, but you will not take my Kenzi.
呃，幸好及时赶到，你个街机小霸王
Uh, followed you just in time, sketch bag.
来吧
Come on.
噢，太谢谢了
Oh.Thank you!
救了我
For saving me!
Kenz
Kenz.
你从什么时候开始单飞了，哈？
Since when do you fly solo, huh?
我回来了，我们回来了，亲们回来了唷，要一起啊
I'm back, we're back, baby got back. Together-like.
听着，我认识这些人，我和他们打过电话
Look, I know these guys. Like, called them know them.
啥？你现在也开始搞捆绑艺术了？
What? You're into getting zip-tied now?
不，我知道是谁打劫了我们。但这是我的问题，我自己能解决
No, I know who robbed us. But it's my problem and I can handle it.
嘿，这是我们的问题，走一起去把我们的东西拿回来
Hey, it's our problem. Let's get our shit back.
不过这些都什么人啊？
So who is this guy, anyway?
Massimo
Massimo.
那个德鲁伊Massimo？
Druid Massimo?
你认识？
You know him?
对，没错，而且他烂透了
Yeah, I do. And he sucks.
毛骨悚然的德鲁伊啊
... creepy druid.
Bo，在未知平面吃苦了吗？
Bo.Tough times in parts unknown?
不过你也不会记得
Not that you would remember.
你的那盅符文水根本没啥用啊
Your rune glass potion fell flat.
是吗，我倒不觉得它失效了
Yeah, I'm not so sure that it did.
谢谢你用亲吻来封印了啊
Thanks to the seal from your kiss.
玻璃樽符文药水，接下来还有什么？
Rune-glass-potion-what-now?
要是我封印了什么东西我很乐意有知情权
I like to know when I'm sealing something.
他给了Tamsin一剂药水来杀我
He gave Tamsin a potion to kill me.
事实上是用来标记你的，让你能穿越
Actually, to mark you. Allow you to transcend planes;
能被逮到
to be collected.
防止Tamsin没有成功的一个保险措施而已
An insurance policy in case Tamsin didn't pan out.
结果她死了，真可惜
It's a shame that she died.
悲了个剧
Tragic.
是谁要带走我？
Who took me?
真不巧，我只是被雇来交货的
Unfortunately,I was just hired to deliver the goods.
肯定有什么是我能告诉你的
There must be something I can tell you...
哎呀....神马都木有
Nah.There's nothing.
好吧，我来告诉你事情该怎么进展
Well here's how this is gonna go
你把我们的东西还回来
You're gonna give us our stuff back
然后你不能再骚扰Kenzi
and then you're gonna leave Kenzi alone.
她再也不需要你的服务了
She won't be requiring your services any longer.
这解决不了她欠我的债
That doesn't settle her debt.
不能？那照你裆部来一脚怎么样？
No?How about a knee to your euro-sack?
好了好了，我们用大人的方式来解决吧
Okay, okay why don't we just handle this like adults?!
异种，德鲁伊，人类，汇集到一起
Fae,Druid,human ... comin' together.
世界和平，我们都是相亲相爱一家人
Peace on Earth.We are the world.
之类的...
Kind of... stuff.
我有个提议
I have a proposal.
恩，现在变成了三个人提议了
Mm,here comes the threesome request.
3P神马的下次再说吧
Let's bank the trio idea 'til next time.
日本猪毛菜碱草，很稀有
The Japanese Salsola Soda herb.It's very rare.
但我听说光明派里医生家的植物墙上种的有
But I hear it grows on the Light Fae Doctor's green wall.
你想让我去Lauren那？
You want me to go to Lauren's?
你认识她么？
Do you know her?
你把那东西给我，我们就扯平了
You get it for me, and we're even.
我的刀？
Geraldine?
我要把这个拿回来。我们的东西怎么办？
I'm taking this back. What about our stuff?
你可以把还没烧掉的拿回去 我可是在帮你 相信我
You'll get back what I haven't burnt.Did you a favour,trust me.
就那些口音表？
Those accent tables?
好吧，我们会拿到你要的草药的
Fine. We'll get you the herb.
但如果你还想继续讨价还价
But if you don't hold up your end of the bargain,
我一定会杀了你的
I'll kill you.
还有我的梳子，你可以留着
And my hairbrush?You can keep.
因为这一点儿都不恶心
Because that's not creepy at all...
我们被监视了
We're being watched.
你找到我了 现在想怎样？
You found me.Now what?
油毡布一号下面是什么？
What's behind tarp number one?
他们想要我们去看
They want us to look.
他们耍的小把戏 姐玩腻了的
Play their little game.I'm done playing.
我和你睡了
I slept with you...
噢 水晶妹
Oh Crystal.
不
No.
是他们强迫的，为了要控制你
Because they made me. To keep you close.
然后，那个之后……我……我不知道
But then, after I did...I ... I don't know.
一切都变了，你懂吗，多了点什么
It was different, you know? It was more.
啊，美人计
Ahh.Spy-banged.
我错过了什么吗？
Did I miss something?
我也干过一样的事
I've been here before.
事实上，感同身受
In your shoes,actually.
我有个兄弟
I have a brother.
我唯一的手足，密不可分
My only sibling. We were inseparable.
我们要一起改变世界来着
Together, we were going to change the world.
听起来不错
Sounds nice.
是，曾经是不错
Yeah,yeah it was.
然后就变质了
Until it wasn't anymore.
我们要改变世界的观念变成了
Our version of changing the world turned into
用炸弹炸毁输油管道
blowing up pipelines using pipe bombs.
*生态恐怖分子常干的事，炸输油管道，撞捕鱼船等*
死了11个人
Eleven people died.
你是个恐怖分子？
You're a terrorist?
本来那应该没有人的
Nobody was supposed to be there...
我没有一天不在悔恨自己的所做所为
Not a day goes by that I don't hate myself for what happened.
这不是你的错
It wasn't your fault.
是我制造的炸药
I made the explosives.
我交给了我信任的兄弟
And then I trusted my brother with them.
那他现在在哪
Where is he now?
重点是，Karen跑了
Point is, is that Karen ran.
从那之后我就一直在逃亡
And I have been running ever since.
我不知道我干嘛告诉你
I don't even know why I'm telling you this.
我从来没跟Bo说过
I never even told Bo.
真是感人肺腑，现在，看看油毡布下面
Moving story.Now, look under the tarp.
我想我现在还没放弃游戏
I guess I'm not done playing games just yet.
一小时内一个长老需要你的诊断
An elder needs your diagnosis within the hour.
要不Crystal就死
Or Crystal dies.
这不是什么环境恐怖主义，这是光明派的破烂
This isn't about eco terrorism. This is Light Fae bullshit.
我在试图理解中，肯子，真的
I'm trying to understand, Kenz, really, I am.
你为啥会去找那个何弃疗
Why would you ever go to that nutbag?
我烦死大家让我“快走”
I was tired of everyone telling me to "go".
我不想“走”去其他地方，我想和你一起战斗
I don't want to "go" anywhere.I want to fight with you.
但你一直都是这么做的啊
But you do. You always have.
我以为很简单，你懂的
Look, I thought it'd be simple, you know.
去见Massimo，做个交易
Go see Massimo. Make a deal.
成为异种，但却是暂时的
Become Fae. But it turned out to be temporary.
而且还有点副作用
And a little on the chintzy side.
你花了多少钱？
How much did it cost you?
再一个草药，亲
One more herb, baby.
哦，我好高兴这些看起来都差不多
Phew! Well I'm glad these all look identical.
当你需要Lauren的时候她在哪
Where's Lauren when you need her?
怀念你的前任了？
Ex nostalgia attack?
你知道吗，Taft这个事还是让我很困扰
You know, this whole Taft thing still baffles me.
我说， Lauren很聪明，说不定她没被骗
I mean, Lauren is smart! I mean, maybe she wasn't tricked.
也许她想为他工作，从他那那些报偿什么的
Maybe she wanted to work for him, you know, get something from him?
比如，养老金？
Like...a pension?
我不知道
I don't know.
显然我俩关系的基础
Apparently the foundation of our entire relationship
就是各种隐瞒
was based on "not knowing".
恩，好吧，不管怎么说
Well, look, for whatever it's worth
我觉得Lauren应该是好人
I think that Lauren's one of the good ones.
我还以为你和Dyson一边呢
I always thought you were on Dyson.
上？啥，啥上？你说啥呢？
On? What... what on? What do you mean?
哦你懂，狼叔队的，这是啥？
Oh, you know, Team Wolf. What is this?
是真的，她不叫Lauren
It's true.Her name is not Lauren.
她叫Karen,Karen Beattie
It's Karen. Karen Beattie.
好吧，不算什么特性感的绰号
Okay, not the sexiest moniker.
大概知道为啥她改名了
Kinda get why she might have changed it.
我不认识她
I didn't know her.
别这样，不是那样的
Come on babe, that's not true.
不，我都不知道她叫啥
No, I don't even know her name!
她现在估计又换名字了
And now she's probably changed it again.
开始新的生活，在某个安全的
Started a new,better life. Somewhere safe...
远离我的地方
away from me.
喂，你还好吧
Look, you okay over there?
哦，对，就是在我前任家里
Oh, yeah. Just hangin' in my ex's apartment.
找破烂，我挺好
Finding weird shit. I'm fine.
为毛每个人都要骗我
What is it that makes everyone in my life lie to me?
除了你。这就是为什么我爱你
Except for you. That's why I love you.
哦，天啊，我找到了
Oh my god, I found it!
啊，果然我爱你
Ah,also why I love you.
你在门口放火圈了？
Did you rim the door?
没啊
No.
反向鬼火圈，Trick说过这个
Ignis Rim Converterent. Trick mentioned this.
这个不让异种出去
Instead of keeping Fae out, it locks them in.
Massimo肯定见到我们了
Massimo must have seen ours...
他成功的从傻x升级到了超级傻x了
And he just graduated from a-hole to douche.
好吧，让我试下穿不穿得过去
Okay, let me try crossing.
提醒一下，老娘的化纤外套超级易燃
Warning: My poly-blend jacket is highly flammable.
躺下就滚，亲爱的，躺下就滚
Drop and roll, baby. Drop and roll.
好，好吧
Okay, okay...
我嘞个大去，痛死我老娘我了
Ah! Oh god! It stings like a mother!
Massimo在耍什么烂招呢
What sick game is Massimo playing?
噢，噢，噢，噢
Oh,ow! Ow,ow.
嘿
Hey.
Dyson你知道吗
Dyson. Guess what?
我查了8次Lauren的语音信箱和快餐店的电话号码
I found Lauren's voicemail and the clubhouse number eight times!
震惊了吧！你当然震惊死了
Are you impressed? Yeah you are.
最后一次电话是两天前
This last call was two days ago.
我要去调那条高速附近所有电话记录
I'm gonna pull records from all businesses and pay phones along that highway.
准备好划更多的重点吧
Get ready for more highlighting.
哇这个好重哦，我是个好警察吗?
Oh. This is heavy. Was I a good cop?
你很强
You were tough.
运气不好的时候你会……像个怪兽
On a bad day, you could be a real... monster.
你觉得伦家长得丑！
You think I'm hideous!
连强盗看见我的脸都被吓跑了！
Even the robbers ran away when they saw my face!
我说的怪兽是指好的那种，好吧？
I meant monster in a good way, okay?
你说的根本没道理啊！
That doesn't even make sense!
嘘！小声点
Shh! Please.
Bo是你女朋友吗？
Is Bo your girlfriend?
不，她不是
No. She is not.
但你想让她当你女朋友吧？
But do you want her to be?
我想过，但一个树上的大妈把我的爱拿走了
I did... but then a lady in a tree took my love away.
当我拿回来的时候，Bo已经有女朋友了
And by the time I got it back, Bo had a girlfriend.
你应该以“很久很久以前”开头
You forgot to start with 'once upon a time'.
*面向小朋友的童话书的标准开头*
很久很久以前……我们就没个合适的时候。剧终
Once upon a time... we never found the right time. The End.
爱是神马感觉？
What does love feel like?
我们真滴要讨论这个么？
Are we really doing this?
你感觉到了，你就知道了
When you feel it, you'll know it.
失去的时候，你会想你再也不要失去了
And when it's gone, you'll never want to lose it again.
你知道吗，你和Bo跟Kenzi讨论这吧
You know what, talk to Bo and Kenzi about this stuff, okay?
这真不是我的特长
It's really not my bag.
我不能和Bo说，她讨厌我因为我是黑暗派的
I can't talk to Bo. She hates me because I'm Dark.
那个，是每个人选择的
Well,everyone makes a choice.
不是我，是我之前的我
Not me. It was the me before me.
嘛，或许有天你会选得更好
Well,maybe someday you'll get to make a better choice.
又或许不会，反正不是我的问题
Maybe not. It's not my problem.
你干吗酱刻薄嘛？！
Why do you have to be so mean?!
你干嘛这么多问题
Why do you have so many questions?!
我不信他居然还防Kenzi，他算到了我的能力
I can't believe he Kenzi-proofed it. He's playing off my power.
那我们怎么能让你不冒火花？
How do we make you stop sparking?
恩，它自己会停
Ugh,it kinda just runs out.
你懂的，就跟防晒霜一样，下水以后重新涂
You know, like sunscreen. Reapply after swimming.
我要不洗个澡算了
I guess I can take a shower...
但我……不想把头发弄湿
but I... I really don't want to get my hair wet.
这是种折磨
It's an ordeal.
我听见了
I hear ya.
你造吗，都一星期了，我可能也该洗洗了
You know what though, it's been a week. I probably should wash it.
Lauren的护发素是不是最糟的？
Is Lauren's conditioner the worst?
确实最糟糕
It's the worst.
那里面有保湿剂吗？
Does it even contain humectants?
天知道那女人把什么放她头发上
God knows what that woman puts in her hair.
都不能相信她
She cannot be trusted.
不知道你，但我香波里需要点桃子
I don't know about you I need a little peach in my shampoo.
焕然一新
Refreshing.
来吧妹子
Attagirl.
恩，要是能去除这个魔法的人
Now, if the only one who can remove a rim
只能是设下魔法的人
is the one who set it...
不，我们得搞乱它
No,we have to scramble it.
需要八卦镜和食人魔眼睛各一个，我像Trick吗？
One Pakua Mirror and ogre eye, required.Am I the new Trick?
你能找到那些东西吗？
Can you get all that stuff?
咱俩才认识？
Have you met me?
好吧，我会救你的，别管Trick了，我是Bo2.0
Okay, I'm gonna save your ass. Forget Trick, I'm the new Bo!
好
Okay.
让我可以自由的去爱
"For giving me the freedom to love."
我确实
And I do.
谁在那
Who's there?
流浪者？
...Wanderer?
你要以为我会让你再抓我一次
If you think that I'm gonna let you take me again?
你可算找错淫妖了
You are messing with the wrong Succubus!
我来了 我来了 我来了
I'm here I'm here I'm here.
嘛里嘛里哄
Ignis adflicto affligo.
我做到了！太好了！
I did it! Yes!
Bo，发生了什么事
Bo,what happened?
你看到了吗
Did you see it?
我怎么了？
What's happening to me?
这都是我的错
This is all my fault.
不，不是。你怎会知道他在笼子放了什么
No, it's not. How could you know what he kept in that cage?
Bo，听我说
Bo,listen to me...
我会解决的
I'm gonna take care of this.
我欠他的，Massimo，一屁股的债
I owe him! Massimo. A lot.
好吧，然后我还偷了东西付账给他
Okay, and I've been stealing to pay him.
肯子
Kenz.
从Trick那
From Trick!
Kenzi！
Kenzi!
还有Hale
And from Hale.
我把圣枝也给他了
I gave him the Twig of Zamora.
你疯了？！等等，我不知道那个是啥诶
Are you crazy!? Wait, I don't know what that is.
他就不停的要债啊要债啊
And he just keeps taking
可弄来弄去还是不够永久的能力啊
and taking and it's still not enough for a permanent power.
但我不得不啊，你是人类你就会被带走，Bo！
But I had to do something.Claimed humans are being taken,Bo!
嘿，我不会让任何人带走你的
Hey. I would never let anyone take you.
真的吗？可是我最后一次被检查之后你才回来啊
Really? Because last I checked you just got back.
我受够了这么无助了
And I am tired of feeling helpless.
不能……根本不可能
Not able to..."not able."
等等，谁说的？
Wait,who ever said that?
异种！每一个人！
The Fae! Everybody!
人人都在提醒我
Always reminding me;
我弱爆了，我超没用，我就是个包袱
that I'm weak and I'm vulnerable and I'm a liability
我还是个贼，我还……我亲了Dyson
and a thief and...I kissed Dyson.
啥？
What?
我亲了Dyson
I kissed Dyson.
更扯的是，我觉得其实我唯一想亲的人是Hale
And the worse part is that, I think I only really want to kiss Hale.
我想我爱……喜欢他
I think I... love... like him.
大概吧，我也不知道，我只是好孤单
Maybe? I don't even know. I'm just alone.
不，你并不孤单，Kenzi，你还有我
No,you are not alone,Kenzi,You have me.
我有你……我有大家……可真有什么事
I have you... I have all of you...but when it comes down to it
你们谁也不在我身边，对吧
I don't really have any of you. Do I?
你丢下过我，Bo
You left me,Bo.
你要是再丢下我了呢？
What if you go again?
我就是一个人
I was alone.
没有归属的地方
I belonged nowhere.
不管怎么努力，我都不属于你们之中的一份子
As hard as I try, I'm just not one of you.
圣枝
Zamora Twigs.
从Trick那偷东西，亲狼叔
Stealing from Trick. Kissing Dyson.
我都不知道该怎么吐槽了
I don't even know what is happening anymore.
Bo
然后这些都算了
And of all the things
我茫然的时候，从来没想到过会是你
I'm in the dark about...I never thought it would be you.
我们还没完
We're not done.
哦
Oh...
你好Dyson
Hello Dyson.
Tamsin跟你在一起吗
Is Tamsin with you?
没，我和Kenzi被困在Lauren这了
No,I've been stuck at Lauren's. With Kenzi.
发生了什么事了？
What happened?
不知道，我吵了她，结果她跑了
I don't know, I guess I snapped at her. She took off.
啥？
What?
她就是个小娃娃，连电臀舞都不会跳
She's just a baby, she doesn't even know how to twerk yet!!
恩，她忽然就变成我的旧搭档了
Yeah, well she also suddenly looks like my old partner
午餐时间和九头蛇乱搞的那个
who used to bang Hydras over lunch.
我过来吧
I'm coming to you.
你还看见Massimo拿了我们的什么了？
What else of ours did you see at Massimo's?
我的刀
Geraldine.
我的梳子，抱枕
My hairbrush. Throw pillows.
等等，你用你的梳子给Tamsin梳过头
Wait...you used your brush on Tamsin.
要是他看见上面掉的头发怎么办？
What if he saw her hair in it?
不会，她又不掉头发
No, girl doesn't shed a single lock.
是，但是他是德鲁伊，他可以探测到她的油脂
Yeah, but he's a druid, he still could have detected her oils.
而且他的手下看到个金毛
Plus,his robber saw a blonde girl.
他知道她还活着
He knows she's alive.
对，而且显然Valkyrie的头发出奇的值钱
Yeah, and apparently Valkryie hair is mad valuable.
Massimo没打算让我们死
Massimo didn't want us dead.
没，他只是想引开我们
No,he wanted us distracted.
这样他就能去找他真正想要的东西了
So he could go after what he really wants.
他真正想要的人
Who he really wants.
我一个人去
I'm going alone.
不，不要，不要Bo
No, no, no Bo...
你在这等Dyson吧，你俩挺熟，不是吗
Wait for Dyson. You guys are close, right?
嗨 Tamsin
Hi Tamsin.
你怎么知道我的名字
How do you know my name?
你当然不记得我了
Of course you don't remember me.
但前世我们可是亲密小伙伴唷
But in another life, we were super close.
看
You see?
Kenzi和Bo叫我来的
Kenzi and Bo called me.
让我过来接你
Wanted me to come pick you up.
你也认识她们？
You know them?
我们是最好的盆友了
We are best friends forever.
你是来帮我的对吧？因为我看起来很吓人？
You're here to help me aren't you? It's because I'm hideous?
你很完美
You're perfect.
你干嘛把我绑起来
Why you tie me up?
保护大家,以防你的真身出现
To protect everyone. For when you turn into your true self.
噢，真身？
Ow. My true self?
对，一个怪物
Uh-hunh. A monster.
那我会有麻烦吗？
Am I gonna be in trouble?
哦亲，你本身就是个大麻烦
Oh honey,you are trouble.
*恶搞 The Ambiguously Gay Duo*
*一个以两个性向暧昧的男性超级英雄为主角打击犯罪的动画片*
你跟灭罪百合二人组同住一个屋檐下
You've been playing house with the Ambiguously Fae Duo.
Bo没站队，Kenzi又是个临时异种
Bo's unaligned. Kenzi's temp.
但你，你可是独一无二
But you,you are the real deal.
因为我是黑暗派？
Because I'm Dark?
没错！你坏透了
Exactly! You're bad.
你骨子里就是坏透了
Oh no,it's in your blood.
你变成杀手只是个时间问题
And it's only a matter of time before you become a killer.
这就是为什么你需要我
And that is why you need me.
我杀人？
I kill people?
你想杀Bo，我还帮你了呢
You tried to kill Bo. I helped you.
我们是好拍档
We're a team!
原来这就是为神马Bo会讨厌我
That's why Bo hates me.
习惯吧，像我们这种人
Get used to it. 'Cause people like us?
都会酱孤单一辈子
We die alone.
啊
Anh.
看看这头发
Look at that hair.
那么光泽，又那么年轻
It's so fine. It's so young.
我等这个等了好久，这回终于是我的了
I've waited for this for so long. Now it's finally mine...
唯一能得到年幼Valkyrie头发的方法
and the only way to obtain a young Valkyrie's hair...
就是让它自愿掉下来
is to make it fall out willingly.
啊
Ah!
别给妹子剪她不喜欢的发型
Never give a woman a hair cut she doesn't want.
你得消失了
You need to go.
因为咱俩玩完了
Cuz I'm over you
停下
Stop.
放手
Release.
来见证一下
Witness.
我的七舅老爷啊
Holy shit.
新装备啊
That's new.
不是新
Not new.
是重生
Reborn.
你们长老得的是某种形式的海绵状脑病
Your Elder is suffering from a form of spongiform encephalopathy.
从消化结果来看
The digestive results show
他一直在吸食自己的同类，血亲
that he's been feeding off his own kind,blood relatives.
他得变疯Fae了
He's going Mad Fae.
治疗方法嘛 哦我不知道呢
Course of treatment: Oh, I don't know,
少乱伦一点？
maybe lay off the incest a little bit.
你要知道这些东西根本就不用绑架我
You didn't need to kidnap me to figure this out.
你动下脑子就行了
You just needed to use your brain for once.
因为这个...
Because this...
实在小菜一碟
is child's play!
所以就这样
So here's what's gonna happen.
我同意救你那恶心的长老
I'm gonna agree to treat your disgusting Elder
你得在Crystal过敏性休克之前把她放了
and you're going to free Crystal before she goes into anaphylactic shock
鉴于你破烂的手铐里面有她过敏的镍
from a nickel allergy, due to your antiquated handcuffs.
哦顺便说声啊 还有这个
Oh,and these! By the way...
小菜两碟
are child's play.
你那女友未满的Kenzi
Your not-quite-girlfriend Kenzi...
教了我高端开锁技巧
taught me how to pick a lock.
所以...嗯？我通过你们的奇葩考验了吗？
So... Hm? Did I passed your ridiculous test?
要是我通过了
Because if I did
你就可以出来了，Hale
you can come on out, Hale.
你不是...Hale
You're not... Hale.
我是死亡的前兆
I am a Harbinger of death.
我乘着风祝祷的空气而来
I arrive on winds blessed air.
你不应得的空气
Air that you no longer deserve.
别这样
Please.
Tamsin
Tamsin.
小塔
Lil' T.
我知道你想杀了他
I know you want to kill him.
我也想，相信我
So do I, believe me.
但他不值得
But he's not worth it.
我杀人，我是黑暗派的，记得吗？
I kill. I am Dark, remember?
你不用
You don't have to.
你想成为任何人都可以
You can be whomever you want to be.
你说谎！
You're lying!
你瞧不起我！
You despise me!
好吧，你知道吗
Okay,you know what
你没说错
you're right
前世咱俩可是一路打到底
you and I,we fought in your past life.
你不总是我的菜
You weren't always my favourite.
你触我逆鳞
You rubbed me the wrong way
还侵犯我私人空间
you,uh,could be a real close talker.
可我从来没恨过你
But I never hated you.
事实上
In fact
我觉得你简直不可思议
I thought you were incredible.
这就是爱的感觉
That's what love feels like.
没人可以和我室友打架
No one fights with my roommates
除了我
but me.
现在
Now
去电梯那边，闭上眼
go to the elevator, close your eyes.
把音乐开到很大声，好吗?
Turn the music up real loud, okay?
哇，你看见那个了吗
Wow. Did you see that?
我是说，你要是以为她以前就很强
I mean,if you thought she was powerful before
我的妈呀
Woo.
她刚长翅膀了
She just got her wings.
你知道那代表着什么吗
Do you know what that means?
每月的那几天……
Monthly cramps,bloating......
这是她的最后一次生命
this is her last life.
我想大概你救了我的命
So I guess that means you just saved mine.
我才不会让小盆友干缺德事
I don't let children do my dirty work.
特别某些人用石像鬼来搞老娘
Especially after someone sends gargoyles after me to do their's.
什么石像鬼？
What gargoyles?
我不会上你当的
I'm not falling for this.
不，真的
No, really.
石像鬼是高级走狗
Gargoyles serve a higher authority.
他们攻击威胁到他们主人的人，长老们
They attack whoever threatened their masters. Elder Fae.
哈，那我们扯平了
Hah,so I guess we're even now.
还差得远呢
Not even close.
这就是你能穿过火圈进我家门的原因
That's how you got into our house past the rim.
你是人类
You're human.
我是德鲁伊
I am The Druid.
好吧，你们这些绝望悲催的生物
All right, your desperate, pathetic people
你们要找我
you seek me.
你们需要我
You need me.
你们会尊重我的！
You will respect me!
呵呵 尊重？
Oh,respect?
你以为你想要什么都行？
You think you can just take whatever you want?
你动Tamsin和Kenzi一根毛试试
Go near Tamsin and Kenzi one more time.
你特么敢
I dare you.
可你是异种
But you're Fae.
Kenzi就是个人类
Kenzi's just human.
不，她是家人
No.She is family.
你得把那个还回来
You need to give that back.
我们做个交易吧
How about we make a deal?
你没交易机会了亲
Oh, you are out of deals.
我也没耐心了
And I am out of patience.
把那个给我！
Give it to me!
把它给我
Just give it.
你这是在哭？为了头发？
Are you crying right now? Over hair?
我妈
My Mommy,
她需要这个
she needs it!
我需要她需要我
And I need her to need me.
上有八十老母问题？排队吧你
Mommy issues? Get in line.
求你了
Please.
你真是热锅蚂蚁
You are one hot mess.
说到热
And speaking of hot...
别！！！
No!!!!!!
债还清了，认识你真是积德了
Debt's settled. Nice knowing you.
现在我得进去拿了
Now I need to go get it.
不，Massimo别！
No! Massimo no!
我没有因为Dyson的事生气
I'm not mad about Dyson.
那个什么都不是
It meant nothing.
我知道
I know.
那个标记了我的Druid的药？
That druid potion that marked me?
那个显然是由我封好了的？
That I apparently sealed?
那个需要一个永远不会背叛我的人的吻的...
It needed to be a kiss from someone who would never betray me...
但是我没...
But I did...
不是 听我说
No. Listen.
你跟我 我们很长一段时间以来都是自顾自的
You and me, we were on our own for a very long time.
但是我们还是找到彼此了
But we found each other.
我们总会吵架
And there will be times when we fight.
是因为我们是一家人啊
Because we are family.
但是一家人还是会互相支持
But family sticks together.
嗯，就算是在我们最糟的时候
Yeah, even when we screw up.
你能回来我太高兴了
I'm so glad you're back.
我受够没人帮忙了
And I'm done being helpless.
我受够害怕了
I am done being scared.
我们都受够了
We all are.
然后有个邪恶的怪兽威胁要剪了她头发
and then an evil beast threatened to cut her hair
公主就超生气
that made the princess very angry.
她就长出了好看又神奇的翅膀
And she grew beautiful, magical wings
然后她就俯冲下来
and she swooped down
揪住怪兽的耳朵把他提了起来
and she picked up the monster by his ears
把他丢到一个很远很远的地方去了
and she flew him to a far,far away land.
他再也不会回来伤害谁了
Where he would never return to hurt anyone.
再也不会了
Ever again.
嘘
Shh.
艾玛，提醒一下会死啊
Oh,geeze,give a girl a little warning,will ya.
这里是内部密室啊
The inner sanctum.
而且我一直以为你睡浴缸呢
And all this time I thought you slept in the bathtub.
除了周二无尽排骨欢享
No, only after All-You-Can-Eat-Rib-Tuesdays.
你明白自己无所不能的, 对吧
You know you can do anything, right?
回答错误减一百分
Inaccurate.
不见得吧
Not really.
你不一定要变Fae才能和我们相处
You don't have to be Fae to have a place among us.
你有比这更好的选择
There is a way for you to be more.
我能教你
I can teach you.
只是时间问题 ,不觉得吗?
It's about time, don't you think?
对啊
Yeah!
完全正确
Totally.
是什么 ?
What?
时机一到,我保证说
When the time is right, I promise.
诶哟喂狼叔...
Look at you Wolf Man...
超级奶爸背后隐藏着雷锋心啊
inspiring up all the kids n' shit.
Kenzi...
嗯
Hm?
我跟Lauren失去联系了
I've lost Lauren.
我觉得她有危险了
And I think she's in danger.
我得去找她
I have to find her.
挺不错的嘛
Nice touch.
会咬人的东西可不宜做家居小装饰啊
Nothing like a little home decor with bite.
挤得要死
Tough crowd.
还湿了吧唧的
Also, moist.
你就没想过买个除湿器吗
You ever considered a dehumidifier?
我们还没召唤你出现
You have not been summoned to appear before us.
给你点温馨提示
Here's a little something that you should know.
没人能把我呼来唤去的
No one summons me.
我来去自如
I go where I want, when I want.
要是有什么对我图谋不轨的
And if something tries to hurt me
我该出手时就出手
I deal with it.
你的规矩管不到我
I don't live by your rules.
你的规矩这辈子都管不到我
I will never live by your rules.
你要是因为这个想干掉我
And if you want to kill me for that?
试试看啊
Try.
我们对你的提议不感兴趣
We are not interested in your proposal.
我们的目的是除掉不结盟的淫妖
Our intention was to eliminate the unaligned succubus.
呃，没错
Uh, yeah.
本人就是
Over here.
你的血已经表态了
Your blood has spoken.
你已经选好边了
You have chosen a side.
哪一边
What side?
你是黑暗派
You are Dark.